Yesterday we were commenting here on
ayer estuvimos comentando aquí en
Primicia about the marriage proposal of
Primicia la pedida de matrimonio del
Ji's boyfriend and Yui's girlfriend and she tells him
novio novia de ji y yui le dice que
[Music]
[Música]
yes Oh my G I don't know why they don't kiss,
sí Oh my G no sé por qué no se dan besos
the truth is I don't know what the reason is, it's
la verdad no sé cuál es el motivo es
cultural, Chi told it yesterday The thing is
cultural lo contó ayer chi La Movida es
that in December they are waiting for the
que en diciembre se está esperando que
approval and confirmation of the law that
se apruebe no y se confirme la ley en la
allows same-sex couples to get married
que se pueden casar personas del mismo
in Thailand. So it seems that
sexo en Tailandia Entonces por lo visto
since December they have been considering
desde diciembre ya van manejando la idea
getting married. You know what's happening?
de casarse sabéis qué es lo que pasa que
Since the idea of ​​getting
desde que se va manejando la idea de
married has been discussed, these people have started having
casarse esta gente comienzan los
problems with the Fran thing and all
problemas con el tema de Fran no y todo
that nonsense. We must remind you that, well,
el rollo hay que recordaros que bueno
when these people get married, their
cuando esta gente se casen las
properties will unite.
propiedades se unen